A Guide to the James T. Buck, Landscape Architectural Drawings and Plans Collection, 1966-1984
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
James T. Buck, Landscape Architectural Drawings and Plans, 1966-1984
Library of Virginia
41326
Consists of 133 sheets of mostly pencil on paper and some Diazotypes (96.5 x 125 cm. and smaller).
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Shelley Arthur, Richmond, Virginia, 11 May 2004.
Biographical/Historical Information
James T. Buck graduated from the University of Massachusetts. A long-time assistant to well-known Virginia landscape architect Charles F. Gillette, Buck was the last in a host of professionals employed by Gillette. After his 1956-1967 stint with Gillette, Buck opened his own firm in Richmond, Virginia.
Scope and Content
This accession consists of some of the surviving drawings and plans from the landscape architecture firm of James T. Buck. The format of most of the drawings is pencil on tracing paper, however, some Diazoprint duplicates and single copies are included in the collection. No corresponding client files, financial, or other business records are extant.
These drawings and a number of Buck's commissions were continuations of projects undertaken by his previous employer, Charles F. Gillette. Gillette died in 1967, and Buck completed or altered projects for Gillette's former clients. The style of the drawings are very similar to those produced in Gillette's office.
Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically by client name with unidentified drawings at the end.
Contents List
- Andrews, Ramon - Gate Details, [No location] 5/19/1971, Dimensions: 28 x 30 cm.; Scale: 1/2" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 01)
  Drawn By: James T. Buck, Landscape Architect
- Bank of Middlesex - Planting Plan, Urbanna, Va. 5/23/1969, Dimensions: 43 x 76 cm.; Scale: 1/16" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 02)
  Drawn By: James T. Buck, Landscape Architect; Huff and Morris, Architects, Richmond, Virginia
- Bank of Middlesex - Landscape Plan, Deltaville, Va. 9/9/1980, Dimensions: 45 x 53 cm.; Scale: 1/8" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 02)
  Drawn By: James T. Buck, Landscape Architect, Richmond, Virginia
- Bank of Middlesex - Revised Planting and Additions, Urbanna, Va. 10/7/1981, Dimensions: 63.5 x 91 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 02)
- Bank of Middlesex- Mattaponi Branch - Landscape Plan, Mattaponi, Va. 6/12/1980, Dimensions: 61 x 91 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Paper and pencil, Diazo; Sheets: 2 (Folder 02)
- Barnes, Lawrence M. - Landscape Plan, Richmond, Va. 10/8/1980, Dimensions: 54 x 61 cm.; Scale: 1/8" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 03)
- Bland, R. Tyler, Jr. - Master Layout Plan, West Point, Va. 8/5/1968, Dimensions: 61 x 86 cm.; Scale: 1/8" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 04)
- Brown, Donald S. - Revised Terrace Plan, Richmond, Va. 11/6/1975, Dimensions: 29 x 78 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 05)
- Country Club of Virginia - Proposed Entrance, Richmond, Va. 11/22/1978, Dimensions: 58 x 106.5 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 06)
- Cullen, Richard - Terrace and Fence Layout, Richmond, Va. 4/2/1980, Dimensions: 57.5 x 75 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 07)
- Glen Allen Elementary School - Planting Plan, Glen Allen, Va. 7/21/1978, Dimensions: 76 x 107cm.; Scale: 1" = 50'; Media: Diazo; Sheets: 1 (Folder 08)
- Greenberg, Mosey - Landscape Plan, Richmond, Va. 4/7/1983, Dimensions: 35 x 81 cm.; Scale: 1/8" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 09)
- Heindl - Gate and Wall Fountain, [No location] n.d., Dimensions: 29 x 54 cm.; Scale: 1" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Diazo; Sheets: 2 (Folder 10)
  Drawn By: [James T. Buck, Landscape Architect, Richmond, Virginia]
- Jamerson, W. E. - Details for Entrance, Appomattox, Va. 3/21/1969, Dimensions: 38 x 78 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 11)
- Jones, Bob - Landscape Plan, Richmond, Va. 3/9/1984, Dimensions: 56.5 x 97 cm.; Scale: 1" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 13)
- Jones, Bob - Fence Layout, Henrico Co., Va. 9/12/1983, Dimensions: 57.5 x 91 cm.; Scale: 1" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 13)
- Jones, John S. - Landscape Plan, Richmond, Va. 8/17/1979, Dimensions: 44 x 104 cm.; Scale: 1/8" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 12)
- Kelly, Dan - Pedestal and Platform for St. Francis, Richmond, Va. 4/10/1970, Dimensions: 23.5 x 40 cm.; Scale: 1" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 14)
- Kelly, Dan - Details- Summer House, Richmond, Va. 3/20/1968, Dimensions: 52.5 x 60 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 14)
- King, W. G. - Landscape Plan, Richmond, Va. 10/18/1983, Dimensions: 34 x 65 cm.; Scale: 1/8" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 15)
- Lakeview Baptist Church - Landscape Plan, Richmond, Va. 12/9/1976, Dimensions: 71 x 104 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 16)
- Lane, Kenneth P. - Detail Planting for Residence, Kents Cove, Va. 4/1973, Dimensions: 75.5 x 98.5 cm; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 17)
- Lane, Kenneth P. - General Layout Plan, Kents Cove, Va. 4/1973, Dimensions: 73 x 99 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 17)
- Large, Robert - Landscape Plan, Richmond, Va. 3/1974, Dimensions: 69.5 x 106 cm.; Scale: 1/8" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 18)
- Lawrence, Walter - Landscape Development Plan, Richmond, Va. 4/1977, Dimensions: 96.5 x 125 cm.; Scale: 1" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 1)
- Lawrence, Walter - Garden Construction Plan, Richmond, Va. 5/11/1977, Dimensions: 49.5 x 89.5 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 19)
- Lewis, Andrew M. - Deck Layout, Richmond, Va. 5/4/1981, Dimensions: 47.5 x 72 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 20)
- Lewis-Hinson - Landscape Layout, Richmond, Va. 3/16/1976, Dimensions: 56 x 49.5 cm.; Scale: 1" = 5'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 21)
- Mann-Netherwood - Planting Plan, Richmond, Va. 2/28/1978, Dimensions: 64.5 x 104 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 22)
- Massey, Robert L. - Additional Planting, Richmond, Va. 11/9/1973, Dimensions: 81 x 102 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 1)
- Massey, Robert L. - Landscape Layout Plan, Richmond, Va. 11/2/1972, Dimensions: 72 x 102 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 23)
- Massey, Robert [L.] - Landscape and Layout Plan, Richmond, Va. 9/17/1975, Dimensions: 75 x 79 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 23)
- McGinnis, Bernard - Master Layout Plan, Shipman, Va. 4/30/1973, Dimensions: 60 x 104 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 24)
- McGuire, Hunter - New Terrace and Planting Plan, Richmond, Va. 4/5/1984, Dimensions: 37.5 x 53 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 25)
- McNeill-Giles - Garden Plan, Richmond, Va. 8/11/1978, Dimensions: 29 x 56 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 26)
- Monroe, D. D. - Planting for Residence, White Stone, Va. 2/27/1973, Dimensions: 66.5 x 100.5 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 27)
- Monroe, D. D. - Landscape Layout of Grounds, White Stone, Va. 2/27/1973, Dimensions: 50 x 51 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 27)
- Moore, T. Justine - Swimming Pool Layout, Richmond, Va. 5/12/1981, Dimensions: 61 x 91 cm.; Scale: 1/8" = 1'; Media: Diazo; Sheets: 1 (Folder 28)
- Moss, E. L. - Construction Details, Richmond, Va. 8/31/1971, Dimensions: 75.5 x 59.5 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 29)
- Moyer, R. W. - Landscape Plan, Crozet, Va. 12/13/1978, Dimensions: 46.5 x 97.5 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 30)
- Munford, B. B., III - A Layout Plan, Richmond, Va. 3/8/1968, Dimensions: 66 x 83 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Paper and pencil; Diazo; Sheets: 2 (Folder 31)
- Neblett, Thomas B. - Landscape Layout, Richmond, Va. n.d., Dimensions: 56.5 x 55.5 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 32)
- Noland Company - Landscape Plan- General Office, Newport News, Va. 9/13/1971, Dimensions: 55 x 86.5 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 34)
- Noland, Lloyd U., Jr. - Detail Shower and Foot Wash, Newport News, Va. 5/17/1971, Dimensions: 33 x 62 cm.; Scale: 1" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Diazo; Sheets: 2 (Folder 33)
- Noland, Lloyd U., Jr. - Entrance Court Planting Plan, Newport News, Va. 3/26/1969, Dimensions: 41.5 x 80.5 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 33)
  Drawn By: Marcellus Wright & Partners, Architects; James T. Buck, Landscape Architect, Richmond, Virginia
- Noland, Lloyd U., Jr. - Alterations to Lloyd U. Noland, Jr. Residence, Newport News, Va. 3/18/1971, Dimensions: 610x 92 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Diazo; Sheets: 2 (Folder 33)
  Drawn By: Marcellus Wright and Partners, Architects, Crozet House, 100 E. Main St., Richmond, Virginia 23219
- Noland, Lloyd U., Jr. - Swimming Pool Layout, Newport News, Va. 4/23/1971, Dimensions: 56.5 x 88 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 33)
- Nolde, John A., Jr. - Landscape Plan, Richmond, Va. 4/30/1975, Dimensions: 72 x 86 cm.; Scale: 1" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Diazo; Sheets: 2 (Folder 35)
- Northern Neck State Bank - Landscape Plan, Warsaw, Va. 9/27/1979, Dimensions: 61 x 91 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Paper and pencil, Diazo; Sheets: 2 (Folder 36)
- Okole Maluna Stables - Planting Plan, Manakin-Sabot, Va. 10/20/1972, Dimensions: 68 x 102 cm.; Scale: 1/8" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 37)
- Pamunkey Regional Library- Rockville Branch - Landscape Plan, Rockville, Va. 2/2/1984, Dimensions: 76 x 107 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Diazo; Sheets: 1 (Folder 38)
- Parham Park Office Park - Parham Park Office Park, Executive Center, Richmond, Henrico Co., Va. 7/28/1972, Dimensions: 61 x 91 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Diazo; Sheets: 1 (Folder 39)
  Drawn By: Mastin Associates, Architects, 2964 Peachtree Rd. NW, Atlanta, GA 30305
- Parham Park Office Park - Landscape Plan, Richmond, Henrico Co., Va. 6/19/1973, Dimensions: 62 x 103 cm.; Scale: 1" = 30'; Media: Paper and pencil; Diazo; Sheets: 4 (Folder 39)
- Parry, Howell J., Jr. - Landscape Plan, Richmond, Va. 5/8/1981, Dimensions: 54.5 x 99 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 40)
- Powell Family Section- Hollywood Cemetery - Landscape Plan, [Richmond, Va.] 6/20/1979, Dimensions: 44 x 50 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 41)
- Rainey, Gordon - Swimming Pool Layout, Richmond, Va. 2/16/1981, Dimensions: 29.5 x 53 cm.; Scale: 1/8" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 42)
- Richmond Metropolitan Authority - Second Street Garage, Richmond, Va. n.d., Dimensions: 56 x 91.5 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Blueline; Sheets: 1 (Folder 43)
  Drawn By: Howard Needles Tammen & Bergendoff, Consulting Engineers; Marcellus Wright Cox Climberg & Ladd, Architects, Richmond
- [River Road Baptist Church] - Planting Plan, [Richmond, Va.] n.d., Dimensions: 61 x 91.5 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Diazo; Sheets: 1 (Folder 44)
  Drawn By: Oliver Smith Cooke and Lindner, Architects, Virginia Beach and Richmond, Virginia
- Robertson, Giles, Jr. - New Terrace Plan, Richmond, Va. 1/16/1981, Dimensions: 24.5 x 40 cm.; Scale: 1/8" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 45)
- Salvation Army - Salvation Army Boys Club, Richmond, Va 1/1970, Dimensions: 77 x 107 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Diazo; Sheets: 1 (Folder 46)
  Drawn By: Marcellus Wright and Partners, Architects; James T. Buck, Landscape Architect, Richmond, Virginia
- Saunders, T. Nelson - Fence Details, [Richmond, Va.] 2/13/1976, Dimensions: 43.5 x 62 cm.; Scale: 1/2" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 47)
- Saunders, T. Nelson - Detail Elevations, Richmond, Va. 4/3/1975, Dimensions: 50 x 104 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Diazo; Sheets: 1 (Folder 47)
- Scher, Norman A. - Driveway Layout and Planting Front of Residence, Henrico Co., Va. 1/30/1981, Dimensions: 61.5 x 90 cm.; Scale: 1" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Diazo; Sheets: 1 (Folder 48)
- Scott, Buford - Alteration and Addition to Residence, [No location] 6/19/1975, Dimensions: 45 x 91 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Diazo; Sheets: 1 (Folder 49)
  Drawn By: Marcellus Wright Cox Cilimberg and Ladd, 1501 North Hamilton Street, Richmond, Virginia 23230
- Southampton Memorial Hospital - Site Work for Additions and Alterations to Southampton Memorial Hospital, Landscaping- New Addition and Master Plan, Franklin, Va. 6/18/1970, Dimensions: 76 x 107 cm.; Scale: 1" = 50'; Media: Diazo; Sheets: 1 (Folder 50)
- St. Bartholomew Episcopal Church - The E. Walker Turner Memorial Garden, Richmond, Va. 11/16/1983, Dimensions: 45.5 x 75.5 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 51)
- Starke, Thomas J., III - Pool and Terrace Grading Plan, Richmond, Va. 3/18/1980, Dimensions: 58 x 89 cm.; Scale: 1/8" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 52)
- Starke, Thomas J., III - Pool and Terrace Layout Plan, Richmond, Va. 3/18/1980, Dimensions: 58 x 89 cm.; Scale: 1/8" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 52)
- Starke, Tom - Swimming Pool Layout, Richmond, Va. 6/15/1972, Dimensions: 61.5x 94.5 cm.; Scale: 1/8" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 53)
- Stettinius, Joseph - General Layout and Planting Plan, Richmond, Va. 5/27/1971, Dimensions: 61 x 65 cm.; Scale: 1" = 1'; Media: Diazo; Sheets: 1 (Folder 54)
- Stettinius, Wallace - A General Plan, Richmond, Va. 4/10/1970, Dimensions: 69 x 98 cm.; Scale: 1/8" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 55)
- Sutton, D. N. - Landscape Layout Plan, West Point, Va. 4/15/1980, Dimensions: 74 x 95 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 56)
- Swift, Russell O. - A Garden Plan, Richmond, Va. 12/6/1968, Dimensions: 61 x 75 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 57)
- Terry, Bland - Landscape Development Plan, Richmond, Va. n.d., Dimensions: 82 x 70 cm.; Scale: 1/8" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 58)
- Thornton, William - Office Court Landscape Plan, [Richmond, Va.] 4/29/1981, Dimensions: 32 x 37 cm.; Scale: 1/2" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 59)
- Thornton, William S. - Landscape Plan, Richmond, Va. 1/24/1979, Dimensions: 61 x 92 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Paper and pencil; Diazo; Sheets: 2 (Folder 59)
- Toms, Peter - Fence and Gate Details, Richmond, Va. 8/4/1971, Dimensions: 39.5 x 44 cm.; Scale: 1 1/2" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 60)
- U. S. Navy - Naval Amphibious Base- Dispensary and Dental Clinic Addition- Planting Schedule and Details, Little Creek, Norfolk, Va. n.d., Dimensions: 71 x 102 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Diazo; Sheets: 1 (Folder 61)
  Drawn By: Marcellus Wright Cox & Climberg, Architecture, Planning, and Interior Design
- U. S. Navy - Naval Amphibious Base- Dispensary and Dental Clinic Addition- Planting Plan, Little Creek, Norfolk, Va. n.d., Dimensions: 71 x 102 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Diazo; Sheets: 1 (Folder 61)
- U. S. Postal Service - Landscaping Plan- Ridge Branch Postal Facility, Richmond, Va. n.d., Dimensions: 62 x 93 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Diazo; Sheets: 2 (Folder 62)
- University of Richmond - Construction Details- President's House, Richmond, Va. 4/26/1973, Dimensions: 54 x 102 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 63)
- University of Richmond - Planting Plan- UR Drive Islands, Richmond, Va. 12/6/1979, Dimensions: 42 x 96.5 cm.; Scale: 1/8" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 63)
- University of Richmond - Landscape Plan- Lora Robins Dormitory, Richmond, Va. 1/31/1980, Dimensions: 58 x 89 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 63)
- University of Richmond - Planting Plan- Administrative Complex, Richmond, Va. 11/2/1978, Dimensions: 58 x 90.5 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 63)
- University of Richmond - Walk Layout, Richmond, Va. 5/7/1978, Dimensions: 58 x 91 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 63)
- University of Richmond - Library Planter Planting Plan, Richmond, Va. 9/19/1977, Dimensions: 31 x 49.5 cm.; Scale: 1" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 63)
- University of Richmond - Library Planting Plan, Richmond, Va. 10/14/1976, Dimensions: 77 x 106 cm.; Scale: 1" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 63)
- University of Richmond - Gray Hall- Westhampton College- Landscape Plan, Richmond, Va. 9/27/1974, Dimensions: 64 x 107 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Paper and pencil; Diazo; Sheets: 2 (Folder 63)
- University of Richmond - Gazebo for Lake, Richmond, Va. 11/4/1975, Dimensions: 67 x 100 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 63)
- University of Richmond - Layout Plan for Lake, Richmond, Va. 4/8/1975, Dimensions: 71 x 106.5 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 63)
- University of Richmond - Lake Landscaping Plan, Richmond, Va. 12/11/1975, Dimensions: 64.5 x 102 cm.; Scale: 1" = 50'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 63)
- University of Richmond - Planting Plan- Power Plant Area, Richmond, Va. 9/16/1977, Dimensions: 69.5 x 105 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 63)
- University of Richmond - Planting Plan- Science Building, Richmond, Va. 11/21/1977, Dimensions: 75 x 103 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 63)
- University of Richmond - Plaque Detail, Richmond, Va. n.d., Dimensions: 25.5 x 37 cm.; Scale: Full size; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 63)
- University of Richmond - Tree Planting Plan- Residence for the President, Richmond, Va. 3/6/1972, Dimensions: 57 x 93 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Sepia Diazo; Sheets: 1 (Folder 63)
- University of Richmond - Elevation- Proposed Entrance, Richmond, Va. 10/7/1970, Dimensions: 56 x 106 cm.; Scale: 1/2" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Diazo; Sheets: 2 (Folder 63)
- University of Richmond - Pool Details, Richmond, Va. 7/11/1978, Dimensions: 23 x 76 cm.; Scale: 1/2" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 63)
- University of Richmond - Cannon Memorial Chapel- Landscape Layout, Richmond, Va. 12/20/1979, Dimensions: 49.5 x 102 cm.; Scale: 1/8" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 63)
- University of Richmond - Master Layout Plan- President's Residence, Richmond, Va. 5/3/1973, Dimensions: 69.5 x 97.5 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 63)
- University of Richmond - Landscape Plan Commons Area, Richmond, Va. 12/14/1976, Dimensions: 84 x 104 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder Roll 1)
- University of Richmond - A Woodland Garden, Richmond, Va. 6/12/1970, Dimensions: 76 x 80 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Paper and pencil; Diazo; Sheets: 2 (Folder 63)
- University of Richmond - Fine Arts Building, Richmond, Va. 2/28/1966, Dimensions: 76.5 x 106.5 cm.; Scale: 1" = 50'; Media: Blueline; Sheets: 1 (Folder 63)
- Westinghouse Electric Supply Company - Landscape Plan, Richmond, Va. 5/13/1976, Dimensions: 61 x 92 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Diazo; Sheets: 1 (Folder 64)
- Williams, Fielding - Terrace Layout, Richmond, Va. 6/13/1978, Dimensions: 41 x 51.5 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 66)
- Williams, John D. - Swimming Pool Layout, Richmond, Va. 7/7/1980, Dimensions: 32 x 40.5 cm.; Scale: 1/8" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 65)
- Witt, Luke - Layout and Construction Plan, Richmond, Va. 4/10/1968, Dimensions: 62 x 80; Scale: As noted; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 67)
- Witt, Luke - A Basic Planting Plan, Richmond, Va. 5/8/1968, Dimensions: 58 x 73 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 67)
- Wortham, Virginia - Garden Layout, Richmond, Va. 10/3/1969, Dimensions: 32 x 49 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Diazo; Sheets: 2 (Folder 68)
- Yeocomico Church - Lanscape Plan [Entrance, Church Yard, Cemetery], Westmoreland Co., Va. 9/5/1980, Dimensions: 70.5 x 78 cm. and smaller; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 3 (Folder 69)
- Zeigler, A. W. - Planting Plan, Hartsville, Sc. 8/19/1976, Dimensions: 70 x 103.5 cm.; Scale: 1/8" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 70)
- Zimberg, Yale - Front Layout, Richmond, Va. 7/27/1978, Dimensions: 42.5 x 88 cm.; Scale: 1" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 71)
- Zimberg, Yale - Rear Property Line Wall, Richmond, Va. 7/6/1978, Dimensions: 28 x 55 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 71)
- Zimberg, [Yale] - Trash Can Area, Richmond, Va. 9/27/1976, Dimensions: 30 x 42.5 cm.; Scale: 1/2" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 71)
- [Unidentified] - Landscape Plan- Proposed Professional Building, Richmond, Va. 10/28/1968, Dimensions: 50 x 68 cm.; Scale: As noted; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 72)
  Drawn By: James T. Buck, Landscape Architect, Richmond, Virginia; G. Richard Brown, Thomas A. Gresham- Associated Architects
- [Unidentified] - Gate and Fence Details, [No location] n.d., Dimensions: 44 x 61 cm.; Scale: 1" = 1'; Media: Paper and pencil; Sheets: 1 (Folder 72)